Guide to the Gay travel brochures,1959, 1982-2003.
Gay travel brochures,1959, 1982-2003.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Gay travel brochures, 1959, 1982-2003.
7612
0.1 cubic feet
Publications, printed materials.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Brochures and maps describing vacation destinations for a gay clientele.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Brochures and maps describing vacation destinations for a gay clientele. Includes Montreal, Toronto, Puerto Rico, the U.S. Virgin Islands, Wisconsin, Chicago, Texas, and the areas in the Northeast United States, including Provincetown, Long Island, and Manhattan. Includes 1959 European travel magazines collected by the Mariposa Education and Research Foundation.
SUBJECTS
Subjects:
Gays--Social life and customs.; Gays--Travel.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIALS
Collecting Program: Human Sexuality Collection.
CONTAINER LIST
- Gay Travel Brochures
  - Germany and Copenhagen, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    From Mariposa Collection
  - Michael's of Florida Travel Guide, ca. 1970s (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Manhattan Guide, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - David James Press, 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Columbia Fun Maps, 1992-1997 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Gift of Ian Lekus
  - David James Press: Texas Map, 1992-1997 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Women in Motion (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - It's Only Natural: Gay and Lesbian Travel in Switzerland (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Gay Travel, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Gay Traveller, 1993, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Gay West (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Dinah Shore Weekend, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - RSVP, ca. 1995-2000 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Gay Travel News, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Atlantis, Cruises, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Paris, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 14)